

# **CHARLOTTE CHUCA**

INTERN



+639351639213



lottechuca.edu@gmail.com



1403 St. Jude Dr. Palmera 3&4 Taytay, Rizal

To gain valuable experience, knowledge and skills in a challenging environment to foster those I have learned from school. In return, I offer my determination to be an asset of your company throughout the duration of my training period.

# **Experience**

Freelance Virtual Assistant (Basic Tasks)

2019-2020

**Social Media Manager (Basic Tasks)** 

2020-2021

**Shopify/Amazon Data Entry** 

2020-2021

**Facebook Ads Interests Targeting** 

2022

# **Education**

2017 - 2019

OUR LADY OF FATIMA UNIVERSITY

Senior High School (STEM)

**2019 - Present** 

UNIVERSITY OF RIZAL SYSTEM

**Bachelor of Science in Information System** 

# **Expertise**

- Visual Design
- With creative thinking.
- Knowledge in Microsoft Office Applications.
- Touch-typist at a range of 40 to 50 words per minute at 100% accuracy.
- Teamwork.
- Well- organized.
- Detail oriented.

## **SEMINARS AND TRAININGS**

- Participated in Leadership Training for SSG, SPG, and Adviser
- Virtual Platform Management Using Microsoft
- Virtual Platform Management Using Google Forms
- Laravel PHP Framework Course
- Java Programming
- Virtual Assistance Training Course

### Reference

#### Reuben V. Buencamino

Online Business Manager at ACB Digital Marketing Services **Phone** 

09172401996

#### Rolando Chuca Jr

Axi / Client Due Diligence Team Lead

#### Phone

+63 9217164960

#### Karen Cisnero

Virtual Assistant Agency Owner

#### **Gmail**

karen@karenremotely.com